<CitationData type="case">
  <Section id="Wisconsin">
    <Citation comment="1">Aicher v. Wis. Patients Comp., 2000 WI 98, ¶ 53, 237 Wis. 2d 99, 613 N.W.2d 849.</Citation>
    <Citation>Aicher v. Wis. Patients Comp., 613 N.W.2d 849, 865 (Wis. 2000).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">Strasser v. Transtech Mobile Fleet Serv., Inc., 2000 WI 87, ¶ 60, 236 Wis. 2d 435, 613 N.W.2d 142.</Citation>
    <Citation>Strasser v. Transtech Mobile Fleet Serv., Inc., 613 N.W.2d 142, 155-56 (Wis. 2000).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">Sudgen v. Bock, 2002 WI App 49, 251 Wis. 2d 344, 641 N.W.2d 693.</Citation>
    <Citation>Sudgen v. Bock, 641 N.W.2d 693 (Wis. Ct. App. 2002).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">Blossom Farm Prods. Co. v. Kasson Cheese Co., 134 Wis. 2d 458, 401 N.W.2d 10 (1987).</Citation>
    <Citation>Blossom Farm Prods. Co. v. Kasson Cheese Co., 401 N.W.2d 10 (Wis. 1987).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">Lipke v. Waushara Elec. Coop., 151 Wis. 2d 784, 447 N.W.2d 394 (Ct. App. 1989).</Citation>
    <Citation>Lipke v. Waushara Elec. Coop., 447 N.W.2d 394 (Wis. Ct. App. 1989).</Citation>
    <Comment id="1">In-state references to decisions appearing in Wisconsin Reports should, where possible, include citations to those reports, in parallel with the regional reporter. In addition, in-state references to decisions from 2000 forward should include a medium-neutral citation which, under Wisconsin rules, consists of the year, a court identifier, and a sequential decision number in the format shown here. Pinpoint cites should be to the paragraph numbers assigned by the court.</Comment>
  </Section>
  <Section id="Mississippi">
    <Citation comment="1">Blackledge v. Omega Ins. Co., 98-CA-00380-SCT (¶ 7), 740 So. 2d 295 (Miss. 1998) (en banc).</Citation>
    <Citation>Blackledge v. Omega Ins. Co., 740 So. 2d 295, 299 (Miss. 1998) (en banc).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">ABC Mfg. Corp. v. Doyle, 97-CT-01376-SCT (¶ 14), 749 So. 2d 43 (Miss. 1997) (en banc).</Citation>
    <Citation>ABC Mfg. Corp. v. Doyle, 749 So. 2d 43, 46 (Miss. 1997) (en banc).</Citation>
    <Citation>Hartford Accident &amp; Indem. Co. v. Foster, 528 So. 2d 255 (Miss. 1988).</Citation>
    <Comment id="1">In-state references to decisions from July 1, 1997, forward should include a medium-neutral citation which, under Mississippi rules, consists of the clerk-assigned case number in the format shown here. Pinpoint cites should be to the paragraph numbers assigned by the court.</Comment>
  </Section>
  <Section id="Oklahoma">
    <Citation comment="1">Oliver v. Farmers Ins. of Cos., 1997 OK 71, ¶ 6, 941 P.2d 985.</Citation>
    <Citation>Oliver v. Farmers Ins. of Cos., 941 P.2d 985, 987 (Okla. 1997).</Citation>
    <Citation>ABC Coating Co. v. J. Harris &amp; Sons Ltd., 747 P.2d 271 (Okla. 1987).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">Peacock v. State, 2002 OK CR 21, ¶ 5, 46 P.3d 713.</Citation>
    <Citation>Peacock v. State, 46 P.3d 713, 714 (Okla. Crim. App. 2002).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">State ex rel. Gibson v. 1997 Dodge, 2001 OK CIV APP 130, ¶ 15, 35 P.3d 1009.</Citation>
    <Citation>State ex rel. Gibson v. 1997 Dodge, 35 P.3d 1009, 1013 (Okla. Civ. App. 2001).</Citation>
    <Comment id="1">In-state references to decisions from 1997 forward should include a medium-neutral citation which, under Oklahoma rules, consists of the year, a court identifier, and a sequential decision number in the format shown here. Pinpoint cites should be to the paragraph numbers assigned by the court. Note that the Oklahoma Court of Criminal Appeals rather than the Oklahoma Supreme Court is the state's court of last resort in criminal matters.</Comment>
  </Section>
  <Section id="Delaware">
    <Citation>Reagan v. Del. Ass'n of Prof'l Eng'rs, 577 A.2d 755 (Del. 1990).</Citation>
    <Citation>In re Polaroid Corp. S'holders Litig., 560 A.2d 491 (Del. 1989).</Citation>
    <Citation>Istituto Bancario Italiano SpA v. Hunter Eng'g Co., 449 A.2d 210 (Del. 1981).</Citation>
    <Citation>Bank of Am. Nat'l Trust &amp; Sav. Assoc. v. GAC Props. Credit, Inc., 389 A.2d 1304 (Del. Ch. 1978).</Citation>
  </Section>
  <Section id="Supreme Court">
    <Citation>Brown v. Helvering, 291 U.S. 193, 203 (1934).</Citation>
    <Citation>John Doe Agency v. John Doe Corp., 493 U.S. 146, 159-60 (1934) (Stevens, J., dissenting).</Citation>
    <Citation>Cornish v. D.C. Bd. on Prof'l Responsibility, 117 S. Ct. 547, 136 L. Ed. 2d 430 (1996).</Citation>
    <Citation>Cammisano v. U.S. Senate Permanent Subcomm. on Investigations, 454 U.S. 1084 (1981).</Citation>
    <Citation>Office of Pers. Mgmt. v. Richmond, 496 U.S. 414 (1990).</Citation>
    <Citation>Scott v. Harris, 127 S. Ct. 1769 (2007).</Citation>
    <Citation>Lawrence v. Florida, 166 L. Ed. 2d 924 (2007).</Citation>
    <Citation>Scott v. Harris, 75 U.S.L.W. 4297 (U.S. Apr. 30, 2007).</Citation>
  </Section>
  <Section id="Tax Court">
    <Citation>Allied Equip. Leasing II v. Comm'r, 97 T.C. 575 (1991).</Citation>
  </Section>
  <Section id="North Carolina">
    <Citation comment="1">Chestnut v. Private Inv. Corp., 32 N.C. 363, 373 S.E.2d 542 (1988).</Citation>
    <Citation>Chestnut v. Private Inv. Corp., 373 S.E.2d 542 (N.C. 1988).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">Nolan v. Forsyth Mem'l Hosp., 124 N.C. App. 670, 478 S.E.2d 676 (1996).</Citation>
    <Citation>Nolan v. Forsyth Mem'l Hosp., 478 S.E.2d 676 (N.C. Ct. App. 1996).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">Joyner v. Town of Weaverville, 94 N.C. App. 588, 380 S.E.2d 536, (1989).</Citation>
    <Citation>Joyner v. Town of Weaverville, 380 S.E.2d 536, (N.C. Ct. App. 1989).</Citation>
    <Comment id="1">In-state references to decisions appearing in North Carolina Reports or North Carolina Court of Appeals Reports should, where possible, include citations to them, in parallel with citations to the regional reporter.</Comment>
  </Section>
  <Section id="Arkansas">
    <Citation comment="1">Whiteside v. Russellville Newspapers, Inc., 2009 Ark. 135, 295 S.W.3d 798.</Citation>
    <Citation>Whiteside v. Russellville Newspapers, Inc., 295 S.W.3d 798 (Ark. 2009).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">Magnolia Sch. Dist. No. 14 v. Ark. State Bd. of Educ., 303 Ark. 666, 799 S.W.2d 791 (1990).</Citation>
    <Citation>Magnolia Sch. Dist. No. 14 v. Ark. State Bd. of Educ., 799 S.W.2d 791 (Ark. 1990).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">All City Glass &amp; Mirror v. McGraw Hill Info. Sys. Co., 295 Ark. 520, 750 S.W.2d 395 (1988).</Citation>
    <Citation>All City Glass &amp; Mirror v. McGraw Hill Info. Sys. Co., 750 S.W.2d 395 (Ark. 1988).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">Bronakowski v. Lindhurst, 2009 Ark. App. 513, 324 S.W.3d 719.</Citation>
    <Citation>Bronakowski v. Lindhurst, 324 S.W.3d 719 (Ark. 1990).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">Aetna Cas. &amp; Sur. Co. v. Dyer, 6 Ark. App. 211, 639 S.W.2d 536 (1982).</Citation>
    <Citation>Aetna Cas. &amp; Sur. Co. v. Dyer, 639 S.W.2d 536 (Ark. Ct. App. 1982).</Citation>
    <Comment id="1">In-state references to decisions appearing in Arkansas Reports should, where possible, include parallel citations to those reports. Citations to decisions from 2009 on should instead use the state's medium-neutral citation system.</Comment>
  </Section>
  <Section id="Bankruptcy Courts and Bankruptcy Panels">
    <Citation>Weiner v. Perry, Settles &amp; Lawson, Inc., 208 B.R. 69 (B.A.P. 1st Cir. 1997).</Citation>
  </Section>
  <Section id="Indiana">
    <Citation comment="1">Slater v. Akron Exch. State Bank, 221 Ind. 497, 49 N.E.2d 344 (1943).</Citation>
    <Citation>Slater v. Akron Exch. State Bank, 49 N.E.2d 344 (Ind. 1943).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">Lovko v. Lovko, 179 Ind. App. 1, 384 N.E.2d 166 (1978).</Citation>
    <Citation>Lovko v. Lovko, 384 N.E.2d 166 (Ind. Ct. App. 1978).</Citation>
    <Citation>Arth Main St. Drugs, Inc. v. A-1 Beverage Comm'n, 404 N.E.2d 65 (Ind. Ct. App. 1980).</Citation>
    <Comment id="1">Publication of Indiana Court of Appeals Reports ceased in 1979; Indiana Reports, in 1981. In-state references to decisions appearing in those reports should, where possible, include parallel citations to them.</Comment>
  </Section>
  <Section id="Maryland">
    <Citation comment="1">Three Garden Vill. Ltd. P'ship v. United States Fid. &amp; Guar. Co., 318 Md. 98, 567 A.2d 85 (1989).</Citation>
    <Citation>Three Garden Vill. Ltd. P'ship v. United States Fid. &amp; Guar. Co., 567 A.2d 85 (Md. 1989).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">Mclean Contracting Co. v. Md. Transp. Auth., 70 Md. App. 514, 521 A.2d 1251.</Citation>
    <Citation>Mclean Contracting Co. v. Md. Transp. Auth., 521 A.2d 1251 (Md. Ct. Spec. App.), cert. denied, 527 A.2d 51 (Md. 1987).</Citation>
    <Comment id="1">In-state references to decisions appearing in Maryland Reports or Maryland Appellate Reports should, where possible, include citations to them. Note that the Maryland Court of Appeals is the state's highest court and the Maryland Court of Special Appeals, an intermediate appellate court.</Comment>
  </Section>
  <Section id="Louisiana">
    <Citation comment="1">State v. Smith, 98-1417, p. 15 (La. 6/29/01); 793 So. 2d 1199, 1208.</Citation>
    <Citation>State v. Smith, 793 So. 2d 1199, 1208 (La. 2001).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">Charles v. St. Mary Ironworks, Inc., 96-2923 (La. 3/14/97); 689 So. 2d 1380.</Citation>
    <Citation>Charles v. St. Mary Ironworks, Inc., 689 So. 2d 1380 (La. 1997).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">Wilson v. Grosjean Contractors, Inc., 97-0012 (La. 3/14/97); 690 So. 2d 25.</Citation>
    <Citation>Wilson v. Grosjean Contractors, Inc., 690 So. 2d 25 (La. 1997).</Citation>
    <Citation>Mellon Fin. Servs. Corp. #7 v. Alexander, 551 So. 2d 632 (La. 1989).</Citation>
    <Citation>First Metro. Bank v. Plaia, 386 So. 2d 94 (La. 1980), on remand, 389 So. 2d 870 (La. Ct. App. 1980).</Citation>
    <Citation>Economy Carpets Mfrs. v. Better Bus. Bureau, Inc., 341 So. 2d 555 (La. 1977).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">Siemssen v. Manpower Temp. Servs., 95-80 (La.App. 5 Cir, 5/30/95); 656 So. 2d 1115.</Citation>
    <Citation>Siemssen v. Manpower Temp. Servs., 656 So. 2d 1115 (La. Ct. App. 1995).</Citation>
    <Citation>Roberts v. La. State Univ. Med. Ctr., 554 So. 2d 230 (La. Ct. App. 1989).</Citation>
    <Comment id="1">In-state references to decisions from 1994 forward should include a medium-neutral citation which, under Lousiana rules, consists of the docket number and date in the format shown here.</Comment>
  </Section>
  <Section id="Idaho">
    <Citation comment="1">Kootenai Envtl. Alliance, Inc. v. Panhandle Yacht Club, Inc., 105 Idaho 622, 671 P.2d 1085 (1983).</Citation>
    <Citation>Kootenai Envtl. Alliance, Inc. v. Panhandle Yacht Club, Inc., 671 P.2d 1085 (Idaho 1983).</Citation>
    <Citation>McCorkle v. Nw. Mut. Life Ins. Co., 112 P.3d 838 (Idaho Ct. App. 2005).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">Jones v. Mountain States Tel. &amp; Tel. Co., 105 Idaho 520, 620 P.2d 1305 (Ct. App. 1983).</Citation>
    <Citation>Jones v. Mountain States Tel. &amp; Tel. Co., 620 P.2d 1305 (Idaho Ct. App. 1983).</Citation>
    <Comment id="1">In-state references to decisions appearing in Idaho Reports should, where possible, include citations to them.</Comment>
  </Section>
  <Section id="Wyoming">
    <Citation comment="1">State v. Nelson, 2002 WY 99, ¶ 6, 49 P.3d 185 (Wyo. 2002).</Citation>
    <Citation>State v. Nelson, 49 P.3d 185, 188 (Wyo. 2002).</Citation>
    <Citation>Wagner v. Wyo. Prod. Credit Ass'n, 773 P.2d 927 (Wyo. 1989).</Citation>
    <Comment id="1">In-state references to decisions from 2001 forward should include a medium-neutral citation which, under Wyoming rules, consists of the year, the state postal abbreviation, and a sequential decision number in the format shown here. Pinpoint cites should be to the paragraph numbers assigned by the court. From January 1, 2004, forward the inclusion of a parallel cite is optional.</Comment>
  </Section>
  <Section id="Tennessee">
    <Citation>Reagan v. Tenn. Mun. League, 751 S.W.2d 842 (Tenn. 1988).</Citation>
    <Citation>Franklin Distrib. Co. v. Crush Int'l (U.S.A.), Inc., 726 S.W.2d 926 (Tenn. Ct. App. 1986).</Citation>
  </Section>
  <Section id="Arizona">
    <Citation comment="1">Tom Reed Gold Mines Co. v. United E. Mining Co., 39 Ariz. 533, 8 P.2d 449 (1932).</Citation>
    <Citation>Tom Reed Gold Mines Co. v. United E. Mining Co., 8 P.2d 449 (Ariz. 1932).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">Spurlock v. Santa Fe Pac. R.R. Co., 143 Ariz. 469, 694 P.2d 299 (Ct. App. 1984).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="2">Spurlock v. Santa Fe Pac. R.R. Co., 143 Ariz. 469, 694 P.2d 299 (App. 1984).</Citation>
    <Citation>Spurlock v. Santa Fe Pac. R.R. Co., 694 P.2d 299 (Ariz. Ct. App. 1984).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="2">Johnson Int'l, Inc. v. City of Phoenix, 192 Ariz. 466, 470-71 ¶ 26, 967 P.2d 607, 611-12 (App. 1998).</Citation>
    <Citation>Johnson Int'l, Inc. v. City of Phoenix, 967 P.2d 607, 611-12 (Ariz. Ct. App. 1998).</Citation>
    <Comment id="1">In-state references to decisions appearing in Arizona Reports should, where possible, include parallel citations to those reports.</Comment>
    <Comment id="2">In-state references also generally use this slightly more economical abbreviation of the Court of Appeals. In addition, decisions rendered since January 1, 1998, include paragraph numbers which are generally used, together with rather than instead of page numbers, in in-state pinpoint citations. For more examples, see § 7-500.</Comment>
  </Section>
  <Section id="Iowa">
    <Citation>Iowa Fed'n of Labor v. Iowa Dep't of Job Serv., 427 N.W.2d 443 (Iowa 1988).</Citation>
    <Citation>City of Sioux City v. Bd. of Trs. of Fire Ret. Sys., 348 N.W.2d 643 (Iowa Ct. App. 1984).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">Bates v. Quality Ready-Mix Co., 261 Iowa 696, 154 N.W.2d 852 (1967).</Citation>
    <Citation>Bates v. Quality Ready-Mix Co., 154 N.W.2d 852 (Iowa 1967).</Citation>
    <Comment id="1">Publication of Iowa Reports ceased in 1968. In-state references to decisions appearing in those reports should, where possible, include parallel citations to them.</Comment>
  </Section>
  <Section id="Michigan">
    <Citation comment="1">Booker v Med Pers Pool, 456 Mich 913; 572 NW2d 656 (1997).</Citation>
    <Citation>Booker v. Med. Pers. Pool, 572 N.W.2d 656 (Mich. 1997).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">Renshaw v Coldwater Hous Comm'n, 381 Mich 590; 165 NW2d 5 (1969).</Citation>
    <Citation>Renshaw v. Coldwater Hous. Comm'n, 165 N.W.2d 5 (Mich. 1969).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">Nat'l Ctr for Mfg Scis v City of Ann Arbor, 221 Mich App 541; 563 NW2d 65 (1997).</Citation>
    <Citation>Nat'l Ctr. for Mfg. Scis. v. City of Ann Arbor, 563 N.W.2d 65 (Mich. Ct. App. 1997).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">Gordon Food Serv, Inc v Grand Rapids Material Handling Co, 183 Mich App 241; 454 NW2d 137 (1989).</Citation>
    <Citation>Gordon Food Serv., Inc. v. Grand Rapids Material Handling Co., 454 N.W.2d 137 (Mich. Ct. App. 1989).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">Med. Soc'y of NJ v NJ Dep't of Law &amp; Pub Safety, 183 Mich App 241; 454 NW2d 137 (1989).</Citation>
    <Citation>Med. Soc'y of N.J. v. N.J. Dep't of Law &amp; Pub. Safety, 454 N.W.2d 137 (Mich. Ct. App. 1989).</Citation>
    <Comment id="1">In-state references to decisions appearing in Michigan Reports or Michigan Appeals Reports should, where possible, include citations to them, in parallel with citations to the regional reporter. The format shown above (including the absence of periods called for by The Bluebook and a semi-colon separating the parallel citations) is that set out in the Michigan rules. Those rules deviate in numerous other respects from the citation norms of The Bluebook for both Michigan and out-of-state authority. For those rules and more examples, see § 7-500.</Comment>
  </Section>
  <Section id="Kansas">
    <Citation comment="1">Farmers Ins. Co. v. Sw. Bell Tel. Co., 279 Kan. 976, 113 P.3d 258 (2005).</Citation>
    <Citation>Farmers Ins. Co. v. Sw. Bell Tel. Co., 113 P.3d 258 (Kan. 2005).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">Cent. Fin. Co. v. Stevens, 221 Kan. 1, 558 P.2d 122 (1976).</Citation>
    <Citation>Cent. Fin. Co. v. Stevens, 558 P.2d 122 (Kan. 1976).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">De Graeve v. Sw. Bell Tel. Co., 9 Kan. App. 2d 753, 687 P.2d 1380 (1984).</Citation>
    <Citation>De Graeve v. Sw. Bell Tel. Co., 687 P.2d 1380 (Kan. Ct. App. 1984).</Citation>
    <Citation>Kentucky	Dep't of Revenue v. Isaac W. Bernheim Found., Inc., 505 S.W.2d 762 (Ky. 1974).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">Cement Transp., Inc. v. Hodges, 505 S.W.2d 32 (Ky. App. 1974).</Citation>
    <Citation>Cement Transp., Inc. v. Hodges, 505 S.W.2d 32 (Ky. Ct. App. 1974).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">Louisville Title Mortg. Co. v. Commonwealth, 299 Ky. 224, 184 S.W.2d 963 (1944).</Citation>
    <Citation>Louisville Title Mortg. Co. v. Commonwealth, 184 S.W.2d 963 (Ky. Ct. App. 1944).</Citation>
    <Comment id="1">In-state references to decisions appearing in Kansas Reports or Kansas Court of Appeals Reports should, where possible, include citations to them.</Comment>
    <Comment id="1">In-state references should indicate the deciding court using this slightly different format set out in Kentucky rules.</Comment>
  </Section>
  <Section id="Utah">
    <Citation comment="1">Utah Farm Bureau Ins. Co. v. Crook, 1999 UT 47, ¶ 6, 980 P.2d 685.</Citation>
    <Citation>Utah Farm Bureau Ins. Co. v. Crook, 980 P.2d 685, 686 (Utah 1999).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">Fitz v. Synthes, 1999 UT 103, ¶ 11, 990 P.2d 391.</Citation>
    <Citation>Fitz v. Synthes, 990 P.2d 391, 393(Utah 1999).</Citation>
    <Citation>Arrow Indus., Inc. v. Zions First Nat'l Bank, 767 P.2d 935 (Utah 1988).</Citation>
    <Comment id="1">In-state references to decisions from 1999 forward should include a medium-neutral citation which, under Utah rules, consists of the year, the state postal abbreviation, and a sequential decision number in the format shown here. Pinpoint cites should be to the paragraph numbers assigned by the court.</Comment>
  </Section>
  <Section id="District Courts">
    <Citation>Hollander v. Inst. For Research on Women &amp; Gend. At Columbia Univ., No. 08 Civ. 7286 (LAK) (KNF), 2009 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 34942 (S.D.N.Y. Apr. 15, 2009).</Citation>
    <Citation>Huangyan Imp. &amp; Exp. Corp. v. Nature's Farm Prods., No. 99 Civ. 9404 (SHS), 2000 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 12335 (S.D.N.Y. Aug. 25, 2000).</Citation>
    <Citation>Villar v. Crowley Mar. Corp., 780 F. Supp. 1467 (S.D. Tex. 1992).</Citation>
    <Citation>Diaz v. Antilles Conversion &amp; Exp., Inc., 62 F. Supp. 2d 463 (D.P.R. 1999).</Citation>
    <Citation>Glen Holly Entm't, Inc. v. Tektronix, Inc., 100 F. Supp. 2d 1073 (C.D. Cal. 1999).</Citation>
    <Citation>Perlman v. Swiss Bank Corp. Comprehensive Disability Prot. Plan, 979 F. Supp. 726 (N.D. Ill. 1997).</Citation>
    <Citation>Natural Res. Def. Council v. Fox, 93 F. Supp. 2d 531 (S.D.N.Y. 2000).</Citation>
    <Citation>Chatoff v. West Publ'g Co., 948 F. Supp. 176 (E.D.N.Y. 1996).</Citation>
    <Citation>Haghighi v. Russian-American Broad. Co., 945 F. Supp. 1233 (D. Minn. 1996).</Citation>
    <Citation>Upjohn Co. v. Mova Pharm. Corp., 936 F. Supp. 55 (D.P.R. 1996).</Citation>
    <Citation>N.J. Tpk. Auth. v. PPG Indus., 16 F. Supp. 2d 460 (D.N.J. 1998).</Citation>
    <Citation>Trs. of the Univ. of Pa. v. Mayflower Transit, Civil Action No. 97-1111, 1997 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 14577, (E.D. Pa. Sept. 16, 1997).</Citation>
    <Citation>Azalea Meats, Inc. v. Muscat, 246 F. Supp. 780 (S.D. Fla. 1965).</Citation>
    <Citation>Glinsey v. Baltimore &amp; O.R.R., 356 F. Supp. 984 (N.D. Ohio 1973), rev'd, 495 F.2d 565 (6th Cir. 1974).</Citation>
    <Citation>Post v. Textron, Inc., 554 F. Supp. 419 (W.D. Mich. 1983).</Citation>
    <Citation>Hotchner v. Barrymore, 31 F. Supp. 928 (E.D.N.Y. 1940).</Citation>
    <Citation>Lamkin v. Bowen, 721 F. Supp. 263 (D. Colo. 1989).</Citation>
    <Citation>Allen v. Hunter, 65 F. Supp. 365 (D. Kan. 1946).</Citation>
    <Citation>Navajo Freight Lines v. Bibb, 159 F. Supp. 385 (S.D. Ill. 1958).</Citation>
    <Citation>McRae v. Publ'ns Int'l, 985 F. Supp. 1036 (D. Kan. 1997).</Citation>
    <Citation>Van Houten v. Ralls, 290 F. Supp. 67 (D. Nev. 1967).</Citation>
    <Citation>United States v. Love, 141 F.R.D. 315 (D. Colo. 1992).</Citation>
  </Section>
  <Section id="Oregon">
    <Citation comment="1">Necanicum Inv. Co. v. Emp't Dep't, 345 Or 518, 200 P3d 129 (2008).</Citation>
    <Citation>Necanicum Inv. Co. v. Emp't Dep't, 200 P.3d 129 (Or. 2008).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">Rocky B. Fisheries, Inc. v. N. Bend Fabrication &amp; Mach., Inc., 297 Or 82, 679 P2d 1367 (1984).</Citation>
    <Citation>Rocky B. Fisheries, Inc. v. N. Bend Fabrication &amp; Mach., Inc., 679 P.2d 1367 (Or. 1984).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">Schilling v. SAIF Corp., 109 Or App 494, 820 P2d 471 (1991).</Citation>
    <Citation>Schilling v. SAIF Corp., 820 P.2d 471 (Or. Ct. App. 1991).</Citation>
    <Comment id="1">In-state references to decisions appearing in Oregon Reports or Oregon Reports, Court of Appeals, should, where possible, include citations to them, abbreviated as illustrated above (omitting the periods called for by The Bluebook).</Comment>
  </Section>
  <Section id="Connecticut">
    <Citation comment="1">Tovish v. Gerber Elecs., 212 Conn. 814, 565 A.2d 538 (1989).</Citation>
    <Citation>Tovish v. Gerber Elecs., 565 A.2d 538 (Conn. 1989).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">Hansen v. Ohio Cas. Ins. Co., 239 Conn. 549, 687 A.2d 1262 (1995).</Citation>
    <Citation>Hansen v. Ohio Cas. Ins. Co., 687 A.2d 1262 (Conn. 1995).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">Vogel v. Maimonides Acad. of W. Conn., Inc., 58 Conn. App. 624, 754 A.2d 824 (2000).</Citation>
    <Citation>Vogel v. Maimonides Acad. of W. Conn., Inc.,� 754 A.2d 824 (Conn. App. Ct. 2000).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">Chaleunphone v. Slater Rd. Assocs., 26 Conn. App. 946, 602 A.2d 47 (1992).</Citation>
    <Citation>Chaleunphone v. Slater Rd. Assocs., 602 A.2d 47 (Conn. App. Ct. 1992).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">Bishop's Corner Assocs. Ltd. P'shp v. Serv. Merch. Co., 45 Conn. Supp. 443, 720 A.2d 531 (1997).</Citation>
    <Citation>Bishop's Corner Assocs. Ltd. P'shp v. Serv. Merch. Co., 720 A.2d 531 (Conn. Super. Ct. 1997).</Citation>
    <Comment id="1">In-state references to decisions appearing in Connecticut Reports, Connecticut Appellate Reports, or Connecticut Supplement should, where possible, include citations to them. Indeed, state rules specify that citations in the argument portion of a brief should be to the official reports alone.</Comment>
  </Section>
  <Section id="Montana">
    <Citation comment="1">Prescott v. Innovative Res. Grp., 2010 MT 35, ¶ 19, 355 Mont. 220, 225 P.3d 1253.</Citation>
    <Citation>Prescott v. Innovative Res. Grp., 225 P.3d 1253, 1256 (Mont. 2010).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">Johnson v. Mont. Dep't of Labor &amp; Indus., 240 Mont. 288, 783 P.2d 1355 (1989).</Citation>
    <Citation>Johnson v. Mont. Dep't of Labor &amp; Indus., 783 P.2d 1355 (Mont. 1989).</Citation>
    <Comment id="1">In-state references to decisions appearing in Montana Reports should, where possible, include citations to those reports, in parallel with citations to the regional reporter. In addition, in-state references to decisions from 1998 forward should include a medium-neutral citation which, under Montana rules, consists of the year, the state postal abbreviation, and a sequential decision number in the format shown here. Pinpoint cites should be to the paragraph numbers assigned by the court.</Comment>
  </Section>
  <Section id="California">
    <Citation comment="1">Green v. State of California, 42 Cal. 4th 254, 260, 165 P.3d 118, 121, 64 Cal. Rptr. 3d 390, 393 (2007).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="2">(Green v. State of California (2007) 42 Cal.4th 254, 260.)</Citation>
    <Citation>Green v. State of California, 165 P.3d 118, 121 (Cal. 2007).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">Coal. of Concerned Cmtys., Inc. v. City of Los Angeles, 34 Cal. 4th 733, 101 P.3d 563, 21 Cal. Rptr. 3d 676 (2005).</Citation>
    <Citation>Coal. of Concerned Cmtys., Inc. v. City of Los Angeles, 101 P.3d 563 (Cal. 2005).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">Cal. Educ. Facilities Auth. v. Priest, 12 Cal. 3d 593, 526 P.2d 513, 116 Cal. Rptr. 361 (1974).</Citation>
    <Citation>Cal. Educ. Facilities Auth. v. Priest, 526 P.2d 513 (Cal. 1974).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">Sakotas v. Workers' Comp. Appeals Bd., 80 Cal. App. 4th 262, 95 Cal. Rptr. 2d 153 (2000).</Citation>
    <Citation>Sakotas v. Workers' Comp. Appeals Bd., 95 Cal. Rptr. 2d 153 (Ct. App. 2000).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">Salinas v. Atchison, Topeka &amp; Santa Fe Ry. Co., 5 Cal. App. 4th 1, 6 Cal. Rptr. 2d 446 (1992).</Citation>
    <Citation>Salinas v. Atchison, Topeka &amp; Santa Fe Ry. Co., 6 Cal. Rptr. 2d 446 (Ct. App. 1992).</Citation>
    <Comment id="1">In-state references to decisions appearing in California Reports or California Appellate Reports should, where possible, include parallel citations to them.</Comment>
    <Comment id="2">In addition, they may but need not use the distinctive format employed by the California courts and set out in the California Style Manual. For examples, see § 7-500.</Comment>
  </Section>
  <Section id="Courts of Appeals">
    <Citation>Shames v. Cal. Travel &amp; Tourism Op. Comm'n, 607 F.3d 611 (9th Cir. 2010).</Citation>
    <Citation>Antonov v. Cnty. of Los Angeles Dep't of Pub. Soc. Servs., 103 F.3d 137 (9th Cir. 1996).</Citation>
    <Citation>Chatchka v. Soc'y for Concerned Citizens Interested in Equal., 69 F.3d 666 (5th Cir. 1996).</Citation>
    <Citation>Comm. to Prevent Mun. Bankr. v. Renne, 77 F.3d 488 (9th Cir. 1996).</Citation>
    <Citation>Cong. Fin. v. Commercial Tech., Inc., 74 F.3d 1253 (11th Cir. 1995).</Citation>
    <Citation>Shoemaker v. Accreditation Council for Graduate Med. Educ., 87 F.3d 1322 (9th Cir. 1996).</Citation>
    <Citation>Natural Res. Def. Council v. NRC, 216 F.3d 1180 (D.C. Cir. 2000).</Citation>
    <Citation>Wilson v. Mar. Overseas Corp., 150 F.3d 1 (1st Cir. 1998).</Citation>
    <Citation>Phillips Exeter Acad. v. Howard Phillips Fund, Inc., 196 F.3d 284 (1st Cir. 1999).</Citation>
    <Citation>Grace Bible Fellowship, Inc. v. Me. Sch. Admin. Dist. No. 5, 941 F.2d 45 (1st Cir. 1991).</Citation>
    <Citation>A.B.C. Bus Lines v. Urban Mass Transp. Admin., 831 F.2d 360 (1st Cir. 1987).</Citation>
    <Citation>Orange County Agric. Soc'y, Inc. v. Comm'r, 893 F.2d 529 (2d Cir. 1990).</Citation>
    <Citation>Shiau v. U.S. Dep't of Agric., 895 F.2d 1410 (2d Cir. 1989).</Citation>
    <Citation>S'holders v. Sound Radio, 109 F.3d 873 (3d Cir. 1997).</Citation>
    <Citation>Barry v. Bergen County Prob. Dep't, 128 F.3d 152 (3d Cir. 1997).</Citation>
    <Citation>Tillman v. Lebanon County Corr. Facility, 221 F.3d 410 (3d Cir. 2000).</Citation>
    <Citation>Johnstone v. N. Am. Van Lines, 958 F.2d 363 (3d Cir. 1992).</Citation>
    <Citation>Opticians Ass'n of Am. v. Indep. Opticians of Am., 920 F.2d 187 (3d Cir. 1990).</Citation>
    <Citation>Little Princess Assocs. v. Passgo, Inc. 922 F.2d 832 (3d Cir. 1990).</Citation>
    <Citation>Philadelphia Marine Trade Ass'n v. Local 1242, Int'l Longshoremen's Ass'n, 915 F.2d 1561 (3d Cir. 1990).</Citation>
    <Citation>S.C. State Ports Auth. v. NLRB, 914 F.2d 49 (4th Cir. 1990).</Citation>
    <Citation>Gulf Atl., Inc. v. Gen. Elec. Co., 878 F.2d 1430 (4th Cir. 1989).</Citation>
    <Citation>Stewart Glass &amp; Mirror, Inc. v. U.S. Auto Glass Disc. Ctrs., Inc., 200 F.3d 307 (5th Cir. 2000).</Citation>
    <Citation>Cobb v. Delta Exps., Inc., 186 F.3d 675 (5th Cir. 1999).</Citation>
    <Citation>Moore v. U.S. Auto. Ass'n, 800 F.2d 1147 (5th Cir. 1987).</Citation>
    <Citation>BAW Mfg. Co. v. Slaks Fifth Ave., Ltd., 547 F.2d 928 (5th Cir. 1977).</Citation>
    <Citation>United States ex rel. Interstate Mech. Contrs., Inc. v. Int'l Fid. Ins. Co., 200 F.3d 456 (6th Cir. 2000).</Citation>
    <Citation>Wooddell v. Int'l Bhd. of Elec. Workers, Local 71, 907 F.2d 151 (6th Cir. 1990), rev'd 112 S. Ct. 494 (1991).</Citation>
    <Citation>NLRB v. Dist. 29, 921 F.2d 645 (6th Cir. 1990).</Citation>
    <Citation>Schoonover v. Black Bros. Co., 914 F.2d 258 (6th Cir. 1990).</Citation>
    <Citation>Buchanan v. Apfel, 249 F.3d 485, 2001 FED App. 0138P (6th Cir.).</Citation>
    <Citation>Kennedy v. Nat'l Juvenile Det. Ass'n, 187 F.3d 690 (7th Cir. 1999).</Citation>
    <Citation>Travis v. Gary Cmty. Mental Health Ctr., 921 F.2d 108 (7th Cir. 1990), cert. denied, 112 S. Ct. 60 (1991).</Citation>
    <Citation>A.G. Edwards &amp; Sons, Inc. v. Pub. Bldg. Comm'n, 921 F.2d 118 (7th Cir. 1990).</Citation>
    <Citation>Trs. of Cent. States Health &amp; Welfare Fund v. Lamberti, 878 F.2d 384 (7th Cir. 1989).</Citation>
    <Citation>Hair v. Helena Chem. Co., 915 F.2d 1579 (8th Cir. 1990).</Citation>
    <Citation>Mo. Hous. Dev. Comm'n v. Brice, 919 F.2d 1306 (8th Cir. 1990).</Citation>
    <Citation>Ark. State Bank Comm'r v. Resolution Trust Corp., 911 F.2d 161 (8th Cir. 1990).</Citation>
    <Citation>Crain v. Bd. of Police Comm'rs of the Metro. Police Dep't, 920 F.2d 1402 (8th Cir. 1990).</Citation>
    <Citation>Am. Prof'l Testing Serv. v. Harcourt Brace Jovanovich Legal &amp; Prof'l Publ'ns, 108 F.3d 1147 (9th Cir. 1997).</Citation>
    <Citation>Benton Franklin Riverfront Trailway &amp; Bridge Comm. v. Skinner, 914 F.2d 1496 (9th Cir. 1990).</Citation>
    <Citation>Ins. Co. of Pa. v. Associated Int'l Ins. Co., 922 F.2d 516 (9th Cir. 1990)</Citation>
    <Citation>Morrell Constr. v. Home Ins. Co., 920 F.2d 576 (9th Cir. 1990).</Citation>
    <Citation>Olguin v. Inspiration Consol. Copper Co., 740 F.2d 1468 (9th Cir. 1984).</Citation>
    <Citation>Dillon v. Fibreboard Corp., 919 F.2d 1488 (10th Cir. 1990).</Citation>
    <Citation>Commc'n Workers of Am. v. Southeastern Elec. Coop., 882 F.2d 467 (10th Cir. 1989).</Citation>
    <Citation>Haagen-Dazs Co. v. Masterbrand Distribs., 918 F.2d 183 (11th Cir. 1990).</Citation>
    <Citation>Tally-Ho, Inc. v. Coast Cmty. Coll. Dist., 889 F.2d 1018 (11th Cir. 1989).</Citation>
    <Citation>Nat'l Distrib. Co. v. James B. Beam Distilling Co. 845 F.2d 307 (11th Cir. 1988).</Citation>
    <Citation>Court of Appeals for the Federal Circuit	Or. Steel Mills, Inc. v. United States, 862 F.2d 1541 (Fed. Cir. 1988).</Citation>
  </Section>
  <Section id="West Virginia">
    <Citation comment="1">Syl. pt. 3, Cline v. Paramount Pac., Inc., 156 W. Va. 641, 196 S.E.2d 87 (1973).</Citation>
    <Citation>Cline v. Paramount Pac., Inc., 196 S.E.2d 87 (W. Va. 1973).</Citation>
    <Comment id="1">In-state references to decisions appearing in West Virginia Reports should, where possible, include citations to those reports, in parallel with citations to the regional reporter. Case holdings should, were possible, be cited to syllabus points in the format illustrated.</Comment>
  </Section>
  <Section id="South Carolina">
    <Citation comment="1">Myrtle Beach Seafood Mkt., Inc. v. Rikard, 266 S.C. 52, 221 S.E.2d 399 (S.C. 1976).</Citation>
    <Citation>Myrtle Beach Seafood Mkt., Inc. v. Rikard, 221 S.E.2d 399 (S.C. 1976).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">Carolina Chems., Inc. v. S.C. Dep't of Health &amp; Envtl. Control, 290 S.C. 498, 351 S.E.2d 575 (Ct. App. 1986).</Citation>
    <Citation>Carolina Chems., Inc. v. S.C. Dep't of Health &amp; Envtl. Control, 351 S.E.2d 575 (S.C. Ct. App. 1986).</Citation>
    <Comment id="1">In-state references to decisions appearing in South Carolina Reports should, where possible, include citations to those reports, in parallel with citations to the regional reporter.</Comment>
  </Section>
  <Section id="New Hampshire">
    <Citation comment="1">Psychiatric Inst. of Am. v. Mediplex, Inc., 130 N.H. 125, 536 A.2d 169 (1987), later proceeding, 132 N.H. 177, 564 A.2d 818 (1989).</Citation>
    <Citation>Psychiatric Inst. of Am. v. Mediplex, Inc., 536 A.2d 169 (N.H. 1987), later proceeding, 564 A.2d 818 (N.H. 1989).</Citation>
    <Comment id="1">In-state references to decisions appearing in New Hampshire Reports should, where possible, include citations to those reports.</Comment>
  </Section>
  <Section id="Massachusetts">
    <Citation comment="1">WBZ-TV4 v. Exec. Office of Labor, 414 Mass. 767, 610 N.E.2d 923 (1993).</Citation>
    <Citation>WBZ-TV4 v. Exec. Office of Labor, 610 N.E.2d 923 (Mass. 1993).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">McKenzie v. Brigham &amp; Women's Hosp., 405 Mass. 432, 541 N.E.2d 325 (1989).</Citation>
    <Citation>McKenzie v. Brigham &amp; Women's Hosp., 541 N.E.2d 325 (Mass. 1989).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">Ne. Avionics, Inc. v. City of Westfield, 63 Mass. App. Ct. 509, 827 N.E.2d 721 (2005).</Citation>
    <Citation>Ne. Avionics, Inc. v. City of Westfield, 827 N.E.2d 721 (Mass. App. Ct. 2005).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">Apahouser Lock &amp; Sec. Corp. v. Carvelli, 25 Mass. App. Ct. 1117, 522 N.E.2d 1016 (1988).</Citation>
    <Citation>Apahouser Lock &amp; Sec. Corp. v. Carvelli, 522 N.E.2d 1016 (Mass. App. Ct. 1988).</Citation>
    <Comment id="1">In-state references to decisions appearing in Massachusetts Reports or Massachusetts Appeals Court Reports should, where possible, include citations to them.</Comment>
  </Section>
  <Section id="Vermont">
    <Citation comment="1">Serecky v. Nat'l Grange Mut. Ins., 2004 VT 63, ¶ 15, 177 Vt. 58, 857 A.2d 775.</Citation>
    <Citation>Serecky v. Nat'l Grange Mut. Ins., 857 A.2d 775, 781 (Vt. 2005).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">Ins. Co. of N. Am. v. Miller's Mut. Ins. Ass'n, 139 Vt. 255, 427 A.2d 354 (1981).</Citation>
    <Citation>Ins. Co. of N. Am. v. Miller's Mut. Ins. Ass'n, 427 A.2d 354 (Vt. 1981).</Citation>
    <Comment id="1">In-state references to decisions appearing in Vermont Reports should, where possible, include citations to those reports, in parallel with citations to the regional reporter. In addition in-state references to decisions from 2003 forward should include a medium-neutral citation which, under Vermont rules, consists of the year, the state postal abbreviation, and a sequential decision number in the format shown here. Pinpoint cites should include the paragraph numbers assigned by the court. Vermont rules also call for the use of medium-neutral cites for cases from other jurisdictions that have adopted them.</Comment>
  </Section>
  <Section id="Georgia">
    <Citation comment="1">Retention Alts., Ltd. v. Hayward, 285 Ga. 437, 678 S.E.2d 877 (2009).</Citation>
    <Citation>Retention Alts., Ltd. v. Hayward, 678 S.E.2d 877 (Ga. 2009).</Citation>
    <Citation>Dalcor Mgmt., Inc. v. Sewer Rooter, Inc., 423 S.E.2d 419 (Ga. Ct. App. 1992).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">S &amp; S Mach. Co. v. Intermar S.S. Corp., 189 Ga. App. 13, 374 S.E.2d 767 (1988).</Citation>
    <Citation>S &amp; S Mach. Co. v. Intermar S.S. Corp., 374 S.E.2d 767 (Ga. Ct. App. 1988).</Citation>
    <Comment id="1">In-state references to decisions appearing in Georgia Reports or Georgia Appeals Reports should, where possible, include citations to them.</Comment>
  </Section>
  <Section id="North Dakota">
    <Citation comment="1">Linderkamp v. Hoffman, 1997 ND 64, ¶ 11, 562 N.W.2d 734.</Citation>
    <Citation>Linderkamp v. Hoffman, 562 N.W.2d 734, 737 (N.D. 1997).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">Cont'l Res., Inc. v. Farrar Oil Co., 1997 ND 31, ¶ 12, 559 N.W.2d 841.</Citation>
    <Citation>Cont'l Res., Inc. v. Farrar Oil Co., 559 N.W.2d 841, 845 (N.D. 1997).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">State v. Roberson, 1998 ND App 15, ¶ 12, 586 N.W.2d 687.</Citation>
    <Citation>State v. Roberson, 586 N.W.2d 687, 690 (N.D. Ct. App. 1998).</Citation>
    <Citation>Norden Lab., Inc. v. Rotenberger, 358 N.W.2d 518 (N.D. 1984).</Citation>
    <Citation>Dutchuk v. Bd. of Cnty. Comm'rs, 429 N.W.2d 21 (N.D. Ct. App. 1988).</Citation>
    <Comment id="1">In-state references to decisions from 1997 forward should include a medium-neutral citation which, under North Dakota rules, consists of the year, a court identifier, and a sequential decision number in the format shown here. Pinpoint cites should be to the paragraph numbers assigned by the court.</Comment>
  </Section>
  <Section id="Pennsylvania">
    <Citation comment="1">Blakeney v. Green's Rest., 550 Pa. 689, 704 A.2d 1380 (1997).</Citation>
    <Citation>Blakeney v. Green's Rest., 704 A.2d 1380 (Pa. 1997).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">Beckwith Mach. Co. v. Commonwealth, 485 Pa. 337, 402 A.2d 661 (1979).</Citation>
    <Citation>Beckwith Mach. Co. v. Commonwealth, 402 A.2d 661 (Pa. 1979).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">Bullocks v. Aliquippa &amp; S. R.R. Co., 364 Pa. Super. 642, 525 A.2d 812, appeal denied, 516 Pa. 621, 532 A.2d 19 (1987).</Citation>
    <Citation>Bullocks v. Aliquippa &amp; S. R.R. Co., 525 A.2d 812 (Pa. Super. Ct.), appeal denied, 532 A.2d 19 (Pa. 1987).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">Wells v. Cendant Mobility Fin. Corp., 2006 PA Super 363, ¶ 9, 913 A.2d 929, 933.</Citation>
    <Citation>Wells v. Cendant Mobility Fin. Corp., 913 A.2d 929, 933 (Pa. Super. Ct. 2006).</Citation>
    <Citation>Weaver v. Pa. Bd. of Prob. &amp; Parole, 688 A.2d 766 (Pa. Commw. Ct. 1997).</Citation>
    <Citation>Keystone Outdoor Adver. v. Commonwealth, 687 A.2d 47 (Pa. Commw. Ct. 1996).</Citation>
    <Citation>Rhode Island	Brown &amp; Sharp Mfg. Co. v. King, 404 A.2d 857 (R.I. 1979).</Citation>
    <Comment id="1">In-state references to decisions appearing in Pennsylvania State Reports, Pennsylvania Superior Court Reports, or Pennsylvania Commonwealth Reports should, where possible, include citations to them, in parallel with citations to the regional reporter. The Pennsylvania Superior Court Reports ceased publication in 1998; the Pennsylvania Commonwealth Reports, in 1994. In addition, in-state references to decisions of the Superior Court should include a medium-neutral citation which consists of the year, a court identifier, and a sequential decision number in the format shown here. Pinpoint cites can be to the paragraph numbers assigned by that court.</Comment>
  </Section>
  <Section id="Florida">
    <Citation>Swofford v. Richards Enters., Inc., 515 So. 2d 231 (Fla. 1987).</Citation>
    <Citation>City of N. Miami v. Fla. Defenders of the Env't, 481 So. 2d 1196 (Fla. 1985).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">Gore v. Space Sci. Servs., 697 So. 2d 841 (Fla. 1st DCA 1997).</Citation>
    <Citation>Gore v. Space Sci. Servs., 697 So. 2d 841 (Fla. Dist. Ct. App. 1997).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">S.O.S. Reprod. Sys. of Tampa, Inc. v. Saxon Bus. Prods., Inc., 320 So. 2d 500 (Fla. 3d DCA 1975).</Citation>
    <Citation>S.O.S. Reprod. Sys. of Tampa, Inc. v. Saxon Bus. Prods., Inc., 320 So. 2d 500 (Fla. Dist. Ct. App. 1975).</Citation>
    <Comment id="1">In-state references to decisions of the District Court of Appeal should indicate the district, and in similar fashion references to the Circuit Court should indicate the circuit and references to the County Court, the county. The format for doing so is set out in the Florida rules. For those rules and more examples, see § 7-500.</Comment>
  </Section>
  <Section id="Alaska">
    <Citation>Alaska Far E. Corp. v. Newby, 630 P.2d 533 (Alaska 1981).</Citation>
    <Citation>Parks v. State, 731 P.2d 597 (Alaska Ct. App. 1987).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">Parks v. State, 731 P.2d 597 (Alaska App. 1987).</Citation>
    <Comment id="1">In-state references to Alaska Court of Appeals decisions generally use this slightly more economical format. For more examples, see § 7-500.</Comment>
  </Section>
  <Section id="Hawaii">
    <Citation comment="1">Pac. Concrete Fed. Credit Union v. Kauanoe, 62 Haw. 334, 614 P.2d 936 (1980).</Citation>
    <Citation>Pac. Concrete Fed. Credit Union v. Kauanoe, 614 P.2d 936 (Haw. 1980).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">Krohnert v. Yacht Sys. Haw., Inc., 4 Haw. App. 190, 664 P.2d 738 (1983).</Citation>
    <Citation>Krohnert v. Yacht Sys. Haw., Inc., 664 P.2d 738 (Haw. Ct. App. 1983).</Citation>
    <Comment id="1">In-state references to decisions appearing in Hawaii Reports or Hawaii Appellate Reports should, where possible, include citations to them. Hawaii Appellate Reports ended in 1994. Since 1994, Hawaii Reports have included decisions of both the Hawaii Supreme Court and the Hawaii Intermediate Court of Appeals.</Comment>
  </Section>
  <Section id="Nebraska">
    <Citation comment="1">NI Indus., Inc v. Husker-Hawkeye Distrib., Inc., 233 Neb. 808, 448 N.W.2d 157 (1989).</Citation>
    <Citation>NI Indus., Inc v. Husker-Hawkeye Distrib., Inc., 448 N.W.2d 157 (Neb. 1989).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">Johnson v. Johnson, 15 Neb. App. 292, 726 N.W.2d 194 (2006).</Citation>
    <Citation>Johnson v. Johnson, 726 N.W.2d 194 (Neb. Ct. App. 2006).</Citation>
    <Comment id="1">In-state references to decisions appearing in Nebraska Reports or Nebraska Court of Appeals Reports should, where possible, include citations to those reports.</Comment>
  </Section>
  <Section id="Missouri">
    <Citation>Lewis v. St. Louis Indep. Packing Co., 3 S.W.2d 244 (Mo. 1928).</Citation>
    <Citation>Ex rel. Dir. of Revenue, Mo. v. McKenzie, 936 S.W.2d 590 (Mo. Ct. App. 1996).</Citation>
    <Citation>Imperial Util. Corp. v. Cytron, 673 S.W.2d 858 (Mo. Ct. App. 1984).</Citation>
  </Section>
  <Section id="Ohio">
    <Citation comment="1">Office of Disciplinary Counsel v. Shrode, 95 Ohio St. 3d 137, 2002-Ohio-1759, 766 N.E.2d 597, ¶ 8.</Citation>
    <Citation>Office of Disciplinary Counsel v. Shrode, 766 N.E.2d 597 (Ohio 2002).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">Davis v. Columbus State Cmty. Coll. (1997), 78 Ohio St. 3d 1488, 678 N.E.2d 1227.</Citation>
    <Citation>Davis v. Columbus State Cmty. Coll., 678 N.E.2d 1227 (Ohio 1997).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">Metro. Prop. &amp; Liab. Ins. Co. v. Kott (1980), 62 Ohio St. 2d 114, 116, 403 N.E.2d 985.</Citation>
    <Citation>Metro. Prop. &amp; Liab. Ins. Co. v. Kott, 403 N.E.2d 985, 986 (Ohio 1980).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">Johnston v. Akron Ctr. for Reprod. Health, Inc. (1990), 68 Ohio App. 3d 655, 589 N.E.2d 432, motion overruled, 56 Ohio St. 3d 713, 565 N.E.2d 836.</Citation>
    <Citation>Johnston v. Akron Ctr. for Reprod. Health, Inc., 589 N.E.2d 432 (Ohio Ct. App.), motion overruled, 565 N.E.2d 836 (Ohio 1990).</Citation>
    <Comment id="1">In-state references to decisions appearing in Ohio State Reports, Ohio Appellate Reports, or Ohio Miscellaneous Reports should, where possible, include citations to them. Ohio court practice is to place the year immediately following the parties' names rather than at the end of the citation. In addition, in-state references to decisions from 2002 forward should include a medium-neutral citation which, under Ohio rules, consists of the year, "Ohio", and a sequential decision number in the format shown in the first example. Pinpoint cites can be to the paragraph numbers assigned by the court reporter or, with pre-2002 decisions, to the official report alone.</Comment>
  </Section>
  <Section id="Alabama">
    <Citation>Se. Meats of Pelham, Inc. v. City of Birmingham, 895 So. 2d 909 (Ala. 2004).</Citation>
    <Citation>Talton Telecomm. Corp. v. Coleman, 665 So. 2d 914 (Ala. 1995).</Citation>
    <Citation>Piersol v. ITT Phillips Drill Div., Inc., 445 So. 2d 559 (Ala. 1989).</Citation>
    <Citation>Mims v. Am. Fed'n of Gov't Empls., 531 So. 2d 661 (Ala. 1988).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">Gov't &amp; Civic Empls. Org. Comm. v. Windsor, 262 Ala. 285, 78 So. 2d 646 (1955).</Citation>
    <Citation>Gov't &amp; Civic Empls. Org. Comm. v. Windsor, 78 So. 2d 646 (Ala. 1955).</Citation>
    <Citation>State Dep't of Pub. Health v. Boackle-Phipps Foods, 594 So. 2d 1234 (Ala. Civ. App. 1991).</Citation>
    <Citation>Tracy v. Tracy, 939 So. 2d 48 (Ala. Civ. App. 2006).</Citation>
    <Citation>Sanders v. State, 947 So. 2d 432 (Ala. Crim. App. 2006).</Citation>
    <Comment id="1">Publication of Alabama Reports and Alabama Appellate Court Reports (Ala. App.) ceased in 1976. In-state references to decisions appearing in those reports should, where possible, include parallel citations to them. Note that Alabama has two intermediate appellate courts, one with civil and one with criminal jurisdiction.</Comment>
  </Section>
  <Section id="Illinois">
    <Citation comment="1">Snyder v. Heidelberger, 2011 IL 111052, 953 N.E.2d 415.</Citation>
    <Citation>Snyder v. Heidelberger, 953 N.E.2d 415 (Ill. 2011).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">Linden Bros. v. Practical Elec. &amp; Eng'g Publ'g Co., 309 Ill. 132, 140 N.E. 874 (1923).</Citation>
    <Citation>Linden Bros. v. Practical Elec. &amp; Eng'g Publ'g Co., 140 N.E. 874 (Ill. 1923).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">People v. Hansen, 2011 IL App (2d) 081226, 952 N.E. 82.</Citation>
    <Citation>People v. Hansen, 952 N.E.2d 82 (Ill. App. Ct. 2011).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">Lewis v. Rutland Twp., 359 Ill. App. 3d 1076, 824 N.E.2d 1213 (2005).</Citation>
    <Citation>Lewis v. Rutland Twp., 824 N.E.2d 1213 (Ill. App. Ct. 2005).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">Jastram v. Lake Villa Sch. Dist. 41, 192 Ill. App. 3d 599, 549 N.E.2d 9 (1989).</Citation>
    <Citation>Jastram v. Lake Villa Sch. Dist. 41, 549 N.E.2d 9 (Ill. App. Ct. 1989).</Citation>
    <Comment id="1">In-state references to decisions appearing in Illinois Reports or Illinois Appellate Court Reports should, where possible, include citations to them. Citations to decisions from 2011 on should instead use the state's medium-neutral citation system. Illinois court rules allow, but do not require, parallel citations to the North Eastern Reporter.</Comment>
  </Section>
  <Section id="Minnesota">
    <Citation>Minnegasco, Inc. v. Cnty. of Carver, 447 N.W.2d 878 (Minn. 1989).</Citation>
    <Citation>Great W. Cas. Co. v. Christenson, 450 N.W.2d 153 (Minn. Ct. App. 1990).</Citation>
  </Section>
  <Section id="South Dakota">
    <Citation comment="1">Jansen v. Lemmon Fed. Credit Union, 1997 S.D. 44, ¶ 10, 562 N.W.2d 122, 125.</Citation>
    <Citation>Jansen v. Lemmon Fed. Credit Union, 562 N.W.2d 122, 125 (S.D. 1997).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">Bohlmann v. Lindquist, 1997 S.D. 42, ¶ 13, 562 N.W.2d 578, 581.</Citation>
    <Citation>Bohlmann v. Lindquist, 562 N.W.2d 578, 581 (S.D. 1997).</Citation>
    <Citation>Driscoll v. Great Plains Mktg. Co., 322 N.W.2d 478 (S.D. 1982).</Citation>
    <Comment id="1">In-state references to decisions from 1996 forward should include a medium-neutral citation which, under current South Dakota rules, consists of the year, the state abbreviation (S.D.), and a sequential decision number in the format shown here. Pinpoint cites should include the paragraph numbers assigned by the court.</Comment>
  </Section>
  <Section id="Colorado">
    <Citation comment="1">People v. Padilla-Lopez, 2012 CO 49, ¶ 18, 279 P.3d 651.</Citation>
    <Citation>People v. Padilla-Lopez, 279 P.3d 651, 656 (Colo. 2012).</Citation>
    <Citation>City of Greeley v. Poudre Valley Rural Elec., 744 P.2d 739 (Colo. 1987), appeal dismissed, 485 U.S. 949 (1988).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">B.K. Sweeney Elec. Co. v. Poston, 110 Colo. 139, 132 P.2d 443 (1942).</Citation>
    <Citation>B.K. Sweeney Elec. Co. v. Poston, 132 P.2d 443 (Colo. 1942).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">Vaccaro v. Am. Family Ins. Group, 2012 COA 9, ¶ 18, 275 P.3d 750.</Citation>
    <Citation>Vaccaro v. Am. Family Ins. Group, 275 P.3d 750 (Colo. Ct. App. 2012).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">People v. Petschow, 119 P.3d 495 (Colo. App. 2004).</Citation>
    <Citation>People v. Petschow, 119 P.3d 495 (Colo. Ct. App. 2004).</Citation>
    <Citation>Serv. Merch. Co. v. Schwartzberg, 971 P.2d 654 (Colo. Ct. App. 1997).</Citation>
    <Citation>Vessels Oil &amp; Gas Co. v. Coastal Ref. &amp; Mktg., Inc., 764 P.2d 391 (Colo. Ct. App. 1988).</Citation>
    <Comment id="1">Publication of Colorado Reports ceased in 1980. In-state references to decisions appearing in those reports should, where possible, include parallel citations to them. In addition, in-state references to decisions of the Court of Appeals can follow the practice of the Colorado courts and use a slightly more economic abbreviation of the court. For more examples, see § 7-500. Citations to decisions from 2012 on can use the state's medium-neutral citation system instead of citations to the regional reporter; they need not include a parallel citation.</Comment>
  </Section>
  <Section id="New Jersey">
    <Citation comment="1">Dep't of Envtl. Prot. v. Lennan, 147 N.J. 579, 688 A.2d 1055 (1997).</Citation>
    <Citation>Dep't of Envtl. Prot. v. Lennan, 688 A.2d 1055 (N.J. 1997).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">Essex Cnty. Welfare Bd. v. Dep't of Insts. &amp; Agencies, 75 N.J. 232, 381 A.2d 349 (1978).</Citation>
    <Citation>Essex Cnty. Welfare Bd. v. Dep't of Insts. &amp; Agencies, 381 A.2d 349 (N.J. 1978).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">Diehl v. Diehl, 389 N.J. Super. 443, 913 A.2d 803 (App. Div. 2006).</Citation>
    <Citation>Diehl v. Diehl, 913 A.2d 803 (N.J. Super. Ct. App. Div. 2006).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">Davis v. City of Plainfield, 389 N.J. Super. 424, 913 A.2d 166 (Ch. Div. 2006).</Citation>
    <Citation>Davis v. City of Plainfield, 913 A.2d 166 (N.J. Super. Ct. Ch. Div. 2006).</Citation>
    <Comment id="1">In-state references to decisions appearing in New Jersey Reports or New Jersey Superior Court Reports should, where possible, include citations to those reports. With Superior Court decisions, the division of the court should be indicated: App. Div., Ch. Div. or Law Div.</Comment>
  </Section>
  <Section id="Virginia">
    <Citation comment="1">Government Emps. Ins. Co. v. Moore, 266 Va. 155, 580 S.E.2d 823 (2003).</Citation>
    <Citation>Government Emps. Ins. Co. v. Moore, 580 S.E.2d 823 (Va. 2003).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">Khanna v. Dominion Bank of N. Va., N.A., 237 Va. 242, 377 S.E.2d 378 (1989).</Citation>
    <Citation>Khanna v. Dominion Bank of N. Va., N.A., 377 S.E.2d 378 (Va. 1989).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">First Fed. Sav. &amp; Loan v. Gryder, 909 Va. App. 60, 383 S.E.2d 755 (1989).</Citation>
    <Citation>First Fed. Sav. &amp; Loan v. Gryder, 383 S.E.2d 755 (Va. Ct. App. 1989).</Citation>
    <Comment id="1">In-state references to decisions appearing in Virginia Reports or Virginia Court of Appeals Reports should, where possible, include citations to them, in parallel with citations to the regional reporter.</Comment>
  </Section>
  <Section id="Washington">
    <Citation comment="1">State v. Heddrick, 166 Wn.2d 898, ¶ 20, 215 P.3d 201 (2009).</Citation>
    <Citation>State v. Heddrick, 215 P.3d 201, 206 (2009).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">Shorewood W. Condo. Ass'n v. Sadri, 140 Wn.2d 47, 992 P.2d 1008 (2000).</Citation>
    <Citation>Shorewood W. Condo. Ass'n v. Sadri, 992 P.2d 1008 (Wash. 2000).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">First United Methodist Church of Seattle v. Hearing Exam'r for Seattle Landmarks Pres. Bd., 129 Wn.2d 238, 916 P.2d 374 (1996).</Citation>
    <Citation>First United Methodist Church of Seattle v. Hearing Exam'r for Seattle Landmarks Pres. Bd., 916 P.2d 374 (Wash. 1996).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">People's Org. for Wash. Energy Res. v. Utilities &amp; Transp. Comm'n, 104 Wn.2d 798, 711 P.2d 319 (1985).</Citation>
    <Citation>People's Org. for Wash. Energy Res. v. Utilities &amp; Transp. Comm'n, 711 P.2d 319 (Wash. 1985).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">Cameron v. Murray , 151 Wn. App. 646, ¶ 14, 214 P.3d 150 (2009).</Citation>
    <Citation>Cameron v. Murray, 214 P.3d 150, 155 (2009).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">Graves v. Vaagen Bros. Lumber, Inc., 55 Wn. App. 908, 781 P.2d 895 (1989).</Citation>
    <Citation>Graves v. Vaagen Bros. Lumber, Inc., 781 P.2d 895 (Wash. Ct. App. 1989).</Citation>
    <Comment id="1">In-state references to decisions appearing in Washington Reports or Washington Appellate Reports should, where possible, include citations to them, abbreviated as illustrated above ("Wn." rather than The Bluebook's "Wash."), in parallel with citations to the regional reporter. Pinpoint cites need only use the page numbers in the official report or in the case of decisions issued since 2004 the paragraph numbers appearing in the official report.</Comment>
  </Section>
  <Section id="New York">
    <Citation comment="1">Anderson v. Rehab. Programs Found., 90 N.Y.2d 810, 688 N.E.2d 1381, 666 N.Y.S.2d 99 (1997).</Citation>
    <Citation>Anderson v. Rehab. Programs Found., 688 N.E.2d 1381 (N.Y. 1997).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">Berkowitz v. Chavo Int'l Inc., 74 N.Y.2d 893, 547 N.E.2d 105, 547 N.Y.S.2d 850 (1989).</Citation>
    <Citation>Berkowitz v. Chavo Int'l Inc., 547 N.E.2d 105 (N.Y. 1989).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">M.I.F. Sec. Co. v. R.C. Stamm &amp; Co., 60 N.Y.2d 936, 459 N.E.2d 193, 471 N.Y.S.2d 84 (1983).</Citation>
    <Citation>M.I.F. Sec. Co. v. R.C. Stamm &amp; Co., 459 N.E.2d 193 (N.Y. 1983).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">Medici v. Dalton Sch., Inc., 34 N.Y.2d 735, 313 N.E.2d 789, 357 N.Y.S.2d 496 (1974).</Citation>
    <Citation>Medici v. Dalton Sch., Inc., 313 N.E.2d 789 (N.Y. 1974).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">Schwartz v. Pub. Adm'r, 24 N.Y.2d 65, 246 N.E.2d 725, 298 N.Y.S.2d 955 (1968).</Citation>
    <Citation>Schwartz v. Pub. Adm'r, 246 N.E.2d 725 (N.Y. 1968).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">Brown v. N.Y. City Econ. Dev. Corp., 234 A.D.2d 33, 650 N.Y.S.2d 213 (1st Dep't 1996).</Citation>
    <Citation>Brown v. N.Y. City Econ. Dev. Corp., 650 N.Y.S.2d 213 (N.Y. App. Div. 1996).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">Hugo v. A &amp; A Maint. Enter., 269 A.D.2d 357, 702 N.Y.S.2d 387 (2d Dep't 2000).</Citation>
    <Citation>Hugo v. A &amp; A Maint. Enter., 702 N.Y.S.2d 387 (N.Y. App. Div. 2000).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">Laro Maint. Corp. v. Culkin, 267 A.D.2d 431, 700 N.Y.S.2d 490 (2d Dep't 1999).</Citation>
    <Citation>Laro Maint. Corp. v. Culkin, 700 N.Y.S.2d 490 (N.Y. App. Div. 1999).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">City of New York v. Park S. Assocs., 146 A.D.2d 537, 538 N.Y.S.2d 441 (1st Dep't 1989).</Citation>
    <Citation>City of New York v. Park S. Assocs., 538 N.Y.S.2d 441 (N.Y. App. Div. 1989).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">IBM v. Universal Transcon. Corp., 191 A.D.2d 536, 595 N.Y.S.2d 106 (2d Dep't 1993).</Citation>
    <Citation>IBM v. Universal Transcon. Corp., 595 N.Y.S.2d 106 (N.Y. App. Div. 1993).</Citation>
    <Comment id="1">In-state references to decisions appearing in New York Reports, Appellate Division Reports, or New York Miscellaneous Reports should, where possible, include citations to them. In addition, in-state references to decisions of the Supreme Court Appellate Division should normally indicate the Department.</Comment>
  </Section>
  <Section id="District of Columbia">
    <Citation>Croom v. United States, 546 A.2d 1006 (D.C. 1988).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">Lennon v. United States Theatre Corp., 287 U.S. App. D.C. 202, 920 F.2d 996 (1990).</Citation>
    <Citation>Lennon v. United States Theatre Corp., 920 F.2d 996 (D.C. Cir. 1990).</Citation>
    <Comment id="1">References to decisions of the U.S. Court of Appeals for the D.C. Circuit in briefs submitted to D.C. courts should include citations to the United States Court of Appeals Reports in addition to the Federal Reporter.</Comment>
  </Section>
  <Section id="Military Service Courts of Criminal Appeals">
    <Citation>United States v. Zamberlan, 45 M.J. 491 (C.A.A.F. 1997).</Citation>
    <Citation>United States v. Myers, 25 M.J. 573 (A.F.C.M.R. 1987), petition denied, 27 M.J. 20 (C.M.A. 1988).</Citation>
    <Citation>United States v. Young, 24 M.J. 626 (A.C.M.R. 1987).</Citation>
  </Section>
  <Section id="Texas">
    <Citation>Mariner Fin. Grp., Inc. v. Bossley, 79 S.W.3d 30 (Tex. 2002).</Citation>
    <Citation>Castaldo v. State, 78 S.W.3d 345 (Tex. Crim. App. 2002).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">Birnbaum v. Alliance of Am. Insurers, 994 S.W.2d 766 (Tex. App.—Austin 1999, pet. denied).</Citation>
    <Citation>Birnbaum v. Alliance of Am. Insurers, 994 S.W.2d 766 (Tex. App. 1999).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">Scoggins v. Best Indus. Unif. Supply Co., 899 S.W.2d 276 (Tex. App.—Houston [14th Dist.] 1995, no writ).</Citation>
    <Citation>Scoggins v. Best Indus. Unif. Supply Co., 899 S.W.2d 276 (Tex. App. 1995).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">Walls Reg'l Hosp. v. Altaras, 903 S.W.2d 36 (Tex. App.—Waco 1994, orig. proceeding).</Citation>
    <Citation>Walls Reg'l Hosp. v. Altaras, 903 S.W.2d 36 (Tex. App. 1994).</Citation>
    <Comment id="1">In-state references to decisions of the Texas Courts of Appeals should include a designation of the court plus an indication of any subsequent proceeding in the format shown.</Comment>
  </Section>
  <Section id="Court of Federal Claims">
    <Citation>Ex'r of Estate of Wicker v. United States, 43 Fed. Cl. 172 (1999).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">Express Foods, Inc. v. United States, 229 Ct. Cl. 733 (Cl. Ct. 1981).</Citation>
    <Citation>Youngstown Steel Equip. Sales, Inc. v. United States, 20 Cl. Ct. 517 (1990), rev'd, 935 F.2d 281 (Fed. Cir. 1991).</Citation>
    <Citation>The parenthetical reference "Cl. Ct." must be included in pre-1982 cites to the Ct. Cl. reporter but is unnecessary in cases cited to the Cl. Ct. reporter.</Citation>
  </Section>
  <Section id="Nevada">
    <Citation comment="1">Brisbin v. State Indus. Ins. Sys., 105 Nev. 1024, 810 P.2d 318 (1989).</Citation>
    <Citation>Brisbin v. State Indus. Ins. Sys., 810 P.2d 318 (Nev. 1989).</Citation>
    <Comment id="1">In-state references to decisions appearing in Nevada Reports should, where possible, include citations to those reports.</Comment>
  </Section>
  <Section id="Maine">
    <Citation comment="1">Beale v. Sec'y of State, 1997 ME 82, ¶ 7, 693 A.2d 336.</Citation>
    <Citation>Beale v. Sec'y of State, 693 A.2d 336, 339 (Me. 1997).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">Larochelle v. Hodsdon, 1997 ME 53, ¶ 13, 690 A.2d 986.</Citation>
    <Citation>Larochelle v. Hodsdon, 690 A.2d 986, 989 (Me. 1997).</Citation>
    <Citation>Bazinet v. Concord Gen. Mut. Ins. Co., 513 A.2d 279 (Me. 1986).</Citation>
    <Comment id="1">In-state references to decisions from 1997 forward should include a medium-neutral citation which, under Maine rules, consists of the year, the state postal abbreviation, and a sequential decision number in the format shown here. Pinpoint cites should be to the paragraph numbers assigned by the court.</Comment>
  </Section>
  <Section id="New Mexico">
    <Citation comment="1">Coates v. Wal-Mart Stores, Inc., 1999-NMSC-013, 127 N.M. 47, 976 P.2d 999.</Citation>
    <Citation>Coates v. Wal-Mart Stores, Inc., 976 P.2d 999 (N.M. 1999).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">Golden Oil Co. v. Chace Oil Co., 2000-NMCA-005, ¶ 16, 128 N.M. 526, 994 P.2d 772.</Citation>
    <Citation>Golden Oil Co. v. Chace Oil Co., 994 P.2d 772, 776 (N.M. Ct. App. 2000).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">Gallegos v. Citizens Ins. Agency, 108 N.M. 722, 779 P.2d 99 (1989).</Citation>
    <Citation>Gallegos v. Citizens Ins. Agency, 779 P.2d 99 (N.M. 1989).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">Buckingham v. Health S. Rehab. Hosp., 124 N.M. 419, 952 P.2d 20 (Ct. App. 1997).</Citation>
    <Citation>Buckingham v. Health S. Rehab. Hosp., 952 P.2d 20 (N.M. Ct. App. 1997).</Citation>
    <Citation comment="1">Gallegos v. Yeargin W. Constructors, 104 N.M. 623, 725 P.2d 599 (Ct. App. 1986).</Citation>
    <Citation>Gallegos v. Yeargin W. Constructors, 725 P.2d 599 (N.M. Ct. App. 1986).</Citation>
    <Comment id="1">In-state references to decisions appearing in New Mexico Reports should, where possible, include citations to those reports, in parallel with citations to the regional reporter. In addition in-state references to decisions from 1996 forward should include a medium-neutral citation which, under New Mexico rules, consists of the year, a court identifier, and a sequential decision number in the format shown here. Pinpoint cites should be to the paragraph numbers assigned by the court.</Comment>
  </Section>
</CitationData>
